i wanted to come on and give a bit of an
update
unfortunately i can't do a
record record record five minutes until
one is good enough
because my ipad is broken one of ours
which is my older one won't charge
the other one got shattered and i have
to take the screen to get fixed
and that's the one i normally uh record
on to put up
so um you get less professional you get
less energy
less things put in so
earlier this summer i fell down an mlm
rabbit hole
created meta learning magic to have the
acronym mlm
mlm center for multi-level marketing the
i'm anti-multi-level marketing because
it is a horrific
business the people have a cult-like
following to
they believe that the company can do no
wrong and there's something
in that tension and in that
disconnect between like the worst of
capitalism that somehow
gets benevolent followers that are just
like no you're here for good let us bow
down to you
i don't understand that disconnect and
yet in my not understanding it might not
understand how my friend fell for one of
one of them
my brain created a similar structure
that looks somewhat like an mlm
that saves the world and so in so doing
i was both like okay this is this is a
little strange put it out into the
into the game b community did not get
crickets back although i also got
tension from myself that like i there
was multiple people who wanted were okay
i got the information back right away
when i sent out the video people like
yes i'm interested let's have a
one-on-one conversation
which is much more than i usually get
it's usually maybe one maybe two people
who contact me and i sent it out to like
six or seven and i think i heard back
from every single one of them
and so then they understand that there's
this mlm like structure that they're
into they want to create game b
but i don't how do we work together how
do we work together if i don't
to not have one single hour when we're a
global community and one hour isn't
going to work for everyone especially an
hour that works for me
because the later in my day i get the
more it works for both australia and
europe at the same time but then it
stops working for me in my brain i can
only kind of do it up till about noon
anyway so going through the process of
whenever i have this powerful next step
i go through an existential crisis and i
both like i'm not enough and i'm not
doing this right
and like it's like not happening fast
enough and happening too fast oh my god
what if people know me and i'm gonna
lose my autonomy
like why do i only have 250 subscribers
and oh my god thank god
you know like i can't imagine if i had a
million or i had that that level of um
people listening because i'm both ways
mixing like why are people not listening
and oh my god are people listening to me
that seems really weird
um and being in that tension and being
in that my addictions are more powerful
right now than they normally are
and um my health is not it like i've
been doing these cleanses and it's been
getting slightly better
with my uh fatigue and and the pains
whatever but
my fatigue has gotten slightly better
which helps me move a little more which
doesn't help with the rest of this stuff
but it's just it's in allowing that
process and knowing
although the universe has demanded that
i relax and only do things that are safe
that are fun and easy for me to do i
don't feel like i
constantly want the next thing i'm like
all i have to do is sit back and wait
for the next fire to start
sit back and wait for the next idea and
if it's hard and
if it's not easy for me to do it's not
mine to do so when it was hard it was
hard to have to try and start a six week
course
i was like oh god that means i have to
do this and this and this checklist and
nope
nervous system shuts down i need to go
to sleep and so
um i reached out to carrie or kerry i
remember me and gary and i talked and
she was awesome and she's like listen
we'll sit down we'll figure out how to
do a facebook group
which ironically is not even i created
the facebook page
and i'm like this doesn't work because
when we create events under it
you can't share them they won't you can
only kind of um
what's the word market them pay to have
them
be advertising and unlike when i create
an event in a page and then
anyway i can share it sorry when i
create an event in a group it seems to
allow you to invite it
it's a weird process now i don't know
this because facebook changed
and so there's something very powerful
about this mlm
but i was in this like stuck structure
of like oh god
i need people to understand the
community and i need them to understand
the product
and i need them to want to be i want to
retire people from gay media game b i
want to retire game b
people who are up to amazing things
right now
from game a to game b so they can focus
on their amazing projects
and yet because i'm trying to fix it for
them i'm breaking it for myself because
i'm both like okay how do
you and you and i want you to retire and
i want and it's like right that's not
the same
as them here supporting this project
that's going to retire all of us
and so there was something that kind of
opened up in the last week
that i'm like okay we're starting our
six week course our six week crowd
coaching course
a week from yesterday so on the 20th
we'll be starting we're meeting for six
weeks to discuss
where we are in that topic where we
would like to get to and what's stopping
us and we're crowdsourcing solutions
with
uh i believe there is six of us just in
five of us so far
i think there's room for one more person
and
again i tagged the people because i was
they were the people who were more
interested in the mlm and the
and the game b rather than the product
itself
and yet they're going to be going
through the product and that's kind of
the key is people need to have gone
through a six-week course
in order to be part of this multi-level
um mlm it's not multiple marketing
our mlm is not a learning magic that it
does have a similar structure and part
so you go through a six-week course you
find out
how to improve your life with other
people's ideas no one else is an expert
and in charge of your life you get to
have the final say but you can get ideas
from other people
and see the power of that see the power
in the fifth week of creating a meta
solution
not only can you improve your health
with crowd coaching what could we
improve together with ten thousand
people and a hundred thousand dollars
those are the things we're going to
create together once we get to 10 000
people well how are we getting to 10 000
people because god knows i've had that
number stuck in my head for years now
and now i know how we get there and it's
not by me going viral on youtube
it's not which was never gonna happen
even though that's why i kind of started
was like well eventually i'll get to ten
thousand and then i can start something
nope i'm creating a culture that works
for me
a culture that is authentic and diverse
and inclusive
what can't be authentic and it can be
authentic and uh pretty diverse even
just by myself
even like my morning self versus my
evening self maybe i am diverse on my
own
but there's still only one of me finding
people
who like me right like they
i don't grade on their nerves who
don't i don't want yes men i don't want
people who are supporting what i'm
supporting and just like yeah okay you
go do you
i want people who are truly here to
support this break it
fix it or move along not
either people who want to give me
homework to fix it because that doesn't
work i can't take homework
i can't take homework for myself let
alone other people
um and not like not oh
i need you to do this for me and not you
should do this
like people who are going to come and be
like this needs to get done i'm the one
who do it
and so what i'm doing the mlm structure
helps create that
the structure of the 1 the the hundred
the thousand the ten thousand
is designed so that we're building it
out together and we're thinking okay who
else do we wanna include
can we include people that are diverse
and authentic and
and inclusive because if there's 80
percent of us that are capable of that
of the time that becomes our culture
nobody's capable of that 100 of the time
and
we can't require 100 of the people be
capable of that
or we're going to be a very inclusive
exclusive community
not inclusive and so the people who are
in the beginning need to be the people
who are
like committed to creating game b and
that's part of what breaks it is the
people who are committed to creating
game b already have their own going
on they don't so i want to pause and
work on someone else's project except
this project gives you your project
so if you can't see that you're not
going to get retired through this
well you're not guaranteed to get
returned through this because part of
the beauty of what we are creating is
that for every
person who gets to level five you make
000 you also make 60 000 a year
for 20 other people so there's tons of
room for us to retire
other people who are up to powerful
things but then you have to apply and
work through that system i don't get to
give it to you because i think you're a
good person
so i'm trying to recruit in the good
people now to be like hey come because i
can't guarantee you a spot later that's
when we vote that's when we decide on
those things together
and you will have to go through a
six-week course either way either way
you're gonna have to go through the
six-week course
finding anyway so that's what i'm up to
right now is i'm up to both
just living my life trying to figure out
work-life balance
trying to not let this consume me 24
hours a day seven days a week
which is a near impossibility but it's
coming
as i each level happens and i'm like
once i feel like i'm not truly in this
alone that i could take months off and
it would continue on
then um i think
i'll be able to handle it better and be
able to take that
that breathing room and allow like the
fire has started
it is okay i don't need to start the
next one i don't need to start the next
one i don't even need to wait for the
next one
right now because it's still on me it's
still like the mlm doesn't
multi meta learning magic doesn't exist
until i pick one of those three i picked
the product we are creating it around
the product
and around recruitment around how do we
get to those 10 000 people so if you're
one of the people who's instrumental in
getting to those 10 000
you are going to be one of the people
who gets to 120 000
a year and if you're not and you come on
later great you still get something
awesome you still get a culture of
people
that was created for you from the people
who are now getting 120 000
a year of inclusive diversity a product
that is
powerful and nearly anyone can come
right away and see the beauty in it and
how it's going to improve their life so
that it's worth way more than 25 dollars
per month
and then you get to be part of
everything we create with our combined
contribution of 25
a month
this thing is is huge and it's both a
superior because of that that i'm like
oh every it's just always so close like
there's just this little veil that's
there that like we need to get through
and yet the veil gets thinner and
thinner yet it never completely goes
away
and i think it will once once the 10
people start
start and we're not the 10 people aren't
meeting we're not meeting
it's like there might be two or three of
us who meet weekly everyone else watches
that
and takes on tasks and it's like if
you're willing to take on
actual work of four hours a week you can
be part of the ten
right and so um creating the
the information how to what i just tried
to explain in this one but the actual
material that explains the products
it explains um well the product the six
week course it's free it's not even
twenty foot dollars a month
and wow that leads into the other
products the people get like wait but
we're not paying for it so how is that a
product
i know i know it's the sampler we're
creating all the things that the sampler
leads into
uh the culture that we're creating an
inclusive diverse
you get to make mistakes here there's
room for everyone
i might not sit at a table with you
because i might not be able to stand you
but someone else will we don't cancel
you completely we don't cut you out
because you said something wrong or you
rubbed
me the founder the wrong way right like
i'm very much about creating a world
that works for everyone which means it
has to include everyone
it's just not going to include everyone
from day one if you're somebody who
cannot keep your emotions in check
cannot work with other people cannot
show up and have a conversation for six
weeks in a row
this isn't for you yet right later on
we'll have tools for you to come and
be included in
so stay tuned i'm still going to be
sharing my story and my little
um insights i'll still be sharing and
new fires that come along but i'm not
trying to create them i'm
actively trying to not create them i'm
like okay allow the six-week course
allow that process allow to find the 10
people
or the the handful that's going to find
the 10. help creating that structure so
they know or you say if you're signing
up for 100 here's what you're doing if
you sign up for the thousand here's what
you're doing to sign up for the ten
thousand here's your sign up for the
hundred thousand here's what that means
and no one signs up y'all a hundred
thousand it's like right you're not
commit you're a no if you're
signing up beyond a hundred thousand
because at a hundred thousand
we have a catalog of tools and systems
that already work and are already worth
way more than 25
per month because we've been doing it
for months
years the 10 000 people it's a different
different level that's the level we
start paying 25 bucks a month at and
those people will be people who want to
be part of creating that catalog
want to be part of that hope want to
vote on you want to vote on which apps
we're creating
and both which order and which features
and benefits are in them for their own
life
if you're okay not having to say in that
and just using them then you might want
to be part of the hundred thousand
not be part of that and every level down
the the less
likely you are to make it to sixty to
the three thousand dollars a month
or the ten thousand dollars a month but
you could still be picked as one of the
sixty thousand dollars a year
if you're someone who's contributing
either to this meta learning magic
or to the greater game b creating a
cooperative world
creating a world that is omni-win that
works for everyone is anti-rival risk
you're doing that
i don't care if you call it mlm i don't
care what you call it
if you apply instead of you could get 60
000 a year to work on your projects to
be you
because i don't be me if saving the
world i know that there's tons of other
people out there that are the same
all right this is already getting
upwards of 15 minutes i just wanted to
come in and update because i haven't
been on for a while
and normally i start feeling bad about
that and feel like i'm letting everybody
down
and then now i'm like right now this is
what
this is unfolded in exactly how it's
supposed to i started this youtube
channel i went on to twitter i went onto
instagram because i wanted to
create a world that worked for everyone
and i wasn't comfortable putting myself
out there but i did
it because it was the best next step i
could do
and it's become exactly what it's
supposed to become i don't know if this
channel's
ever gonna have a lot of subscribers
it's not supposed to until it does or
doesn't
it's supposed to and it's done this has
it but it's helped me evolve to the
point where
whatever way through game b i've found
the people to start the six week course
with
and i'm going to work within my
attention of all of my middle child
issues of like oh my god the loyalty and
how do i have a conversation with you
and you and anna how does it come
together
yeah i'm going to deal with that because
it's like
all that good stuff and we're going to
figure out a way to govern and a way to
create a
uh system a structure a governance that
doesn't require
a board meeting that doesn't require
everyone to attend the same meeting that
doesn't because
it's what the world we need globally and
i already had ideas for that so i know
there's ideas on how to do that
it's just about creating the system that
works and creating a
field that we can play on a field that
we can try new things and experiment
both personally
right that i know that i can't truly
fail and never society
my society my community is not going to
let me starve to death
it's not going to let my kids starve to
death if i royally up
and as collectively
even if we up and go bankrupt
that's not real failure
because we're still connected we're
still the next iteration still comes
there is no failure there's like
little failure is encouraged get it
wrong
get it wrong as many times you need on
the road to getting it right
and we're doing it systematically
intelligently we're not
taking on a billion dollar project but
we only have a million dollars
we're not spending money we don't have
we're not spending time we don't have
we're not spending resources we don't
have
and we're working out systematically so
like
what would get you your next improvement
in life that we don't already have
if you wanted to improve your diet how
could that be helped and let's help the
fringes
because the fringe when we help the
fringes they're the ones right if you're
someone who can
do all of that find on your own an app's
gonna help you a tiny bit if you're
someone like me who
lacks executive functioning and cannot
do that on your own
consistently day after day you're going
to be helped immensely by it those are
the people we should probably help you
anyway i've been sharing these
how technology is powerful and there's
tons of people on technology
who are creating the technology
crickets a lot of it gets crickets a lot
of it doesn't have
i know tons of people in there in the
tech space who are amazing human beings
willing to work on things and yet they
still can't get their ideas out into the
world
because people anyway so we're going to
solve that we're going to solve the
number of people the threshold of people
involved in the tech project before it
ever exists
we're going to solve the
the tech you know that the tech people
are taking on the risk therefore it's
it's the startup
culture is basically go broke
or sell the google like go and become a
millionaire by selling it
or you're you're at broken zero
negative because you spent your time and
money on it that there's
so much power when we create things
together and i've been saying that for
years but now we're
actually going to create it together and
we're actually going to move forward
with
how do we create something for six
people how do we how did the ten create
it for themselves
inviting the hundred had a hundred
create it for themselves and invite in a
thousand
and so on and so forth and invite people
to pick
pick the poison which level do you want
to be at if you're level 10
if you're at the second level the 10
person layer
you're gonna be the second i'm the first
one to make it a 220 000
a year then they're the next one and
i've put in the most work
they will have put in the second most
work but we're all going to accumulate
at the top we don't get more power
because of that
we just get paid out first and then
other people get to as well and together
we get to figure out how to retire 20
other people for every one of us
and that's gonna be fun that's gonna be
so much fun to get to
not give out huge amounts of money like
the lottery
but enough for you to live off of enough
for you to be retired
we are going to give individuals
basically passive income
so that they can go and work on their
own projects and if they are
lazy and off to a beach somewhere
we'll all fail together together
and if most of us choose to work on
amazing projects the world can see or
powerful
they're going to continually pay us and
even if we don't even if the one in 20
who
grew this off to a beach somewhere
which i don't
those are people i'm including but even
if we did if we pick the 20 that are up
to big things
it still works so i think there's
something so powerful here
and i'm both extremely excited and
energized and also
scared by it scared that it the wrong
people co-opted or something something
happens or
there's an unforeseen consequence that i
can't perceive
even though that's why i am who i am you
i can see things
not in the future like i'm psychic but
in the future like i'm logical
and can no no you guys are all again
interesting like i don't even know how
other people's brains work so
mine works and i don't necessarily
elevate it above
other people's of anything i'm like
here's all this information i don't have
so i can't be that intelligent i am
and so is everyone else and together
collectively we're going to create the
foundation of information that we can
work off of
we're going to create the tools to
improve our individual lives and help
other people and that's
the basic the basis of who i'm looking
for is people
i'm looking for the people who know me
and know what i'm up to i have to
convince you i'm a powerful person who's
intelligent
you already know me and from there that
they're willing to give their energy and
their expertise to create something
that shows that to other people i don't
need me to be sold to other people
i need the product and the community
that we create together to be sold to
other people marketed to
explained are you on board or not not
sold to
and then yeah we're going to create
something very powerful together so i've
haven't said it in a little bit
but a better world is on its way and
we're all going to get to participate in
co-creating it together
please like and subscribe or don't i
don't kind of give a anymore
if you're already here i appreciate you
if you know somebody who this
is their bread and butter they would
love to be part of saving the world and
creating a better world
invite them those are the people we need
and those are the people we are going to
go out and seek
and bring in and they're going to go
through the six week course which is why
sending a weird random youtube video
that's not very professional be weird
but but there'll be the marketing
material to say hey
just like with an mlm do we have a
business opportunity for you
do we have a world-saving opportunity
for you do you want to come and be a
part of it
and i think anyone who can see the hope
and the magic in what we are doing
in the meta learning magic you can see
the magic you want to be a part of it
all right take care